//Quiz Questions
let quiz = [
    {
        quizNumb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following terminal commands creates an empty html file within the folder named 'test'?",
        answer: " 2. touch ./test/index.html",
        options: [
            " 1. cd test/index.html",
            " 2. touch ./test/index.html",
            " 3. mv ./test/test2 ./test/index.html",
            " 4. mkdir test/index.html"
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 2,
        question: "Which statement is not correct about HTML?",
        answer: " 3. HTML is used to add styling to the elements in a webpage.",
        options: [
            " 1. HTML stands for Hyper Text Markup Language.",
            " 2. HTML can be used to build the structure of a webpage.",
            " 3. HTML is used to add styling to the elements in a webpage.",
            " 4. HTML allows us to define elements like paragraphs, images, links, and forms.",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following Git Commands creates a branch?",
        answer: " 1. git checkout -b <branch name>",
        options: [
            " 1. git checkout -b <branch name>",
            " 2. git pull origin <branch name>",
            " 3. git commit -m <branch name>",
            " 4. git fetch <branch name>",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 4,
        question: "________ is the scripting or programming language that allows you to implement complex features on web pages.",
        answer: " 3. Javascript",
        options: [
            " 1. CSS",
            " 2. API",
            " 3. Javascript",
            " 4. HTML",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 5,
        question : "The _______ allows you to manipulate HTML and CSS, creating, removing and changing HTML.",
        answer: " 2. DOM API",
        options: [
            " 1. Geolocation API",
            " 2. DOM API",
            " 3. WebGL API",
            " 4. None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 6,
        question : "Which of the following examples is not a valid variable name for Javascript?",
        answer: " 4. 10cent",
        options: [
            " 1. $here",
            " 2. _name",
            " 3. sort135",
            " 4. 10cent",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 7,
        question : "What is the correct Javascript syntax to access 2 in the array? const random = ['squid', 795, [0, 1, 2]];",
        answer: " 3. random[2][2]",
        options: [
            " 1. random(0,3)",
            " 2. console.log(random);",
            " 3. random[2][2]",
            " 4. console.log(random.length);",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 8,
        question : "Which of the following does not remove an element from an array?",
        answer: " 4. push()",
        options: [
            " 1. pop()",
            " 2. shift()",
            " 3. splice()",
            " 4. push()",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 9,
        question : "which of the following describes the Javascript function best?",
        answer: " 1. The function definition is also called the function declaration.",
        options: [
            " 1. The function definition is also called the function declaration.",
            " 2. The function consists of the name of the function, and parameters, separated by semi-colon and enclosed in curly braces.",
            " 3. Parameters are essentially passed to functions by variable.",
            " 4. All of the above.",
        ]
    },
    {
        quizNumb: 10,
        question : "Which of the following instance method combines the text of two (or more) strings and returns a new string?",
        answer: " 2. String.prototype.concat()",
        options: [
            " 1. String.prototype.includes()",
            " 2. String.prototype.concat()",
            " 3. String.prototype.at()",
            " 4. String.prototype.substring()",
        ]
    }
];